<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Student Advisement</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="school_of_computing_stud_adv">School of Computing\n Student Advisement</string>
    <string name="school_of_computing">School of Computing</string>
    <string name="student_advisement">Student Advisement</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string name="faq">FREQUENTLY ASKED QUESTIONS</string>
    <string name="que_1">Undergraduate Advising</string>
    <string name="que_2">Contacting Your Advisor</string>
    <string name="que_3">Advisement Week</string>
    <string name="que_4">Registering for Classes</string>
    <string name="que_5">Changing Your Major</string>
    <string name="que_6">Adding a Minor in the School of Computing</string>
    <string name="que_7">Graduation Preparation</string>
    <string name="que_8">How do I contact my professor?</string>
    <string name="que_9">How can I find out when my professor office hours are?</string>
    <string name="que_10">I\'ve emailed my professor but I haven\'t heard back. What should I do? </string>
    <string name="que_11">How do I know who my advisor is?</string>
    <string name="que_12">Why do I need to be advised when I alredy know what classes I want to take?</string>
    <string name="que_13">How will I know when advisement is?</string>
    <string name="que_14">When can I enroll in classes?</string>
    <string name="que_15">I\'ve been advised; Why cant\'t I enroll in classes?</string>
    <string name="que_16">I think I received an unfair grade. Whom can I talk?</string>
    <string name="que_17">What is the difference between a WP and a WF?</string>
    <string name="que_18">What does an NA on my transcript mean?</string>
    <string name="que_19">My incomplete has suddenly turned to a F. What should I do?</string>
    <string name="que_20">All my classes have been dropped from my schedule. What should I do?</string>
    <string name="que_21">How do I get into a closed class?</string>
    <string name="que_22">How do I add or drop a class after the deadline for dropping classes has passed?</string>
    <string name="que_23">I\'m trying to enroll in classes but SOAR won\'t let me?</string>
    <string name="que_24">I\'m feeling overwhelmed, dropped and anxious. Who should I talk to?</string>
    <string name="que_25">I\'m having trouble in on of my classes. How can I get help?</string>
    <string name="que_26">I have a paper due and I don\'t even know where to start?</string>
    <string name="que_27">I signed up for an online class and I don\'t know where to start?</string>
    <string name="que_28">How do I avoid being accused of plagiarism?</string>
    <string name="que_29">I think I have been unfairly accused of plagiarism. What should I do?</string>


    <string name="que1_content">All University of Southern Mississippi students are required to meet with an academic advisor in

their department each semester prior to enrolling in classes.  Your advisor will look over your

degree plan, and work with you to ensure you\'re on track for graduating with your degree. 

Advisors will also help you to make sure that any credits you have from another university or

community college are transferred to Southern Miss, and can help you with probation or

suspension paperwork.</string>
    <string name="que2_content">Your advisor is listed on your SOAR Student Center page. If you do not have an advisor listed,

or you would like to change your advisor, please call the School of Computing office at 601-266-

4949 and we will adjust your official advisor assignment in</string>
    <string name="que3_content">The week before advising begins, the School of Computing office will post the appointment

schedule book on the front desk for sign-up availability. You must come by in person and sign

up.</string>
    <string name="que4_content">After you have been advised, your advisor will give you a form with the list of classes you\'ve

discussed.  You\'ll bring this form to the School of Computing office, and we will remove the

advisement hold from your account.  While you can pre-register for your classes in SOAR even

if you haven\'t been advised, your classes will not be official until your advisement hold is lifted

and will be dropped the last day of the semester.</string>
    <string name="que5_content">If you\'d like to change your major to one of our School of Computing programs, welcome!

Please visit our office in TEC 214 and we will help you get advised and complete the Change of

Major form. The advisor will also sign your form and we will take it for final processing. Within

a week or so, your new major (and a new advisor) should be listed on your SOAR account.</string>
    <string name="que6_content">To add a minor in The School of Computing, please visit our office in TEC 214 and we will help

you get advised and complete the Change of Major form. Within a week, your minor should be

listed in SOAR.  A minor requires 18 hours in the minor area at the 300 or 400 level, and you are

not required to meet an advisor to minor in one of the areas (but, advisement is suggested).  If

you\'d like advisement on your minor, please contact our office in TEC 214.</string>
    <string name="que7_content">Your journey is near completion. For all questions regarding graduation please go to: Graduation

Preparation.</string>
    <string name="que8_content">The best and easiest way to contact any of the School of Computing instructors is by email. Click

here on the university\'s people directory for email addresses and office phone numbers for the

instructors. Please allow up to 48 hours for a response. You can also drop by your professor\'s

office during his/her office hours, which are listed on your syllabus and contact information

sheets are also available in our TEC 214 main office.  If your professor is a graduate instructor or

an adjunct, he/she will not have a phone in the department and is contactable by email or in

person during office hours only. If you are trying to contact your instructor in an online class,

email or Blackboard are your only options. For email addresses of faculty in other

departments, click here for the university\'s police directory </string>
    <string name="que9_content">Your professor’s office hours should be listed on his or her office door and on your syllabus,

which is your first and best resource for information about the class. Contact information sheets

are also available in our TEC 214 main office.  If you are taking an online class, your professor

will not hold office hours and can be contacted by e-mail or Blackboard only.</string>
    <string name="que10_content">Please give your instructors 48 hours to respond to your emails. They may be getting emails

from many, many students, and responding as quickly as they can in the order in which they

received them. If it has been 48 hours and you still haven’t heard, please send the e-mail again,

but copy it to the School of Computing department by typing Sherry.Smith@usm.edu in the cc:

line. This will send a copy to the department undergraduate administrative assistant, who will

make sure it gets to the instructor.</string>
    <string name="que11_content">Your advisor will be listed on your SOAR Student Center page.
        If you do not have an advisor listed, please e-mail the School of Computing department
        undergraduate administrative assistant, Sherry.Smith@usm.edu and we will adjust your information in SOAR.</string>

<string name="que12_content">Your advisor\'s job is to look at your transcript and advise
    you which classes you need to take to graduate in four years with the degree of your choice.
    If you already know the classes you need to take, think of advising as a free degree audit,
    a double-check to make sure you don\'t find yourself missing credits you need when you\'re ready to graduate.
    Even if you are absolutely, positively sure you know what you want to take, advisement is a good
    chance to meet the faculty, who might have interesting suggestions for classes you might want to take in the future.</string>
<string name="que13_content">Advisement dates are listed in the Academic Calendar. You will also see posters
    all over the TEC building and receive notice over the School of Computing listserve. Your advisor may also
    contact you via your USM email address to let you know when he or she will be available during advisement,
    and your advisor\'s office phone number is listed on your SOAR page.</string>
    <string name="que14_content">After you have been advised, please allow your advisor or the office 24 hours
        to check the eligible-to-enroll box on your account, and then check your Student Center for your
        enrollment appointment. General enrollment dates can be found in the Academic Calendar.</string>
    <string name="que15_content">There are a number of reasons that you might be blocked for enrollment.
        It might be that your eligible-to-enroll box has not yet been checked, or it might be that
        there is a hold on your account. A hold on your account could be the result of an unpaid bill,
        a required 099 enrollment that has not been fulfilled, or a hold from the athletic department
        if you are an athlete. You should be able to tell from your Student Center what the problem is by
        clicking on the Do-Not-Enter sign, but if you have any problems, please call the School of Computing
        office at 266-4949 and we will happily check your account to see what has gone wrong and direct you
        to the appropriate person to help you get things sorted out.</string>
    <string name="que16_content">The first person you should talk to is your instructor. Take your
        exam or your paper to your instructor\'s office during his or her office hours to discuss the assignment.
        If you still feel that your grade was unfair, you can make an appointment to talk to the Director of
        the School of Computing, Dr. Andrew Sung.  He will talk to you about your situation, and about the
        grade appeal process. To review the grade appeal process on your own, please click here to
        download a .pdf from USM\'S Student Handbook.</string>
    <string name="que17_content"> A “WP” (withdraw passing) means that you are leaving the class in good standing.
        It will not count against your GPA, although it will remain on your transcript if you are dropping
        the class after the deadline to withdraw without academic penalty. (This deadline will be listed in
        the Academic Calendar. A “WF” means that you are leaving the class failing, and it will count as an “F” in your GPA.
        The decision whether you get a “WP” or a “WF” is based on your performance in the class and is at
        the sole discretion of the instructor.</string>
    <string name="que18_content">“NA” means “not attending” and it is given to students who sign up for a class but don\'t attend it.
        “NAs” count as “Fs” in your GPA, and you will also be charged for the class, as financial aid will not pay for
        a class that you haven\'t attended. Check your schedule at the beginning of the semester and make sure that all
        the classes are ones you plan to attend. If you don\'t plan to go, drop the class while you still can on SOAR,
        and if it is past the deadline, see procedures for dropping a class after the deadline. If you feel
        you have been given an “NA” in error, please contact your instructor.</string>
    <string name="que19_content">Incompletes only stay on your transcript for one semester. If you have not completed
        your work at the end of the following semester (not including summer), the “I” disappears and is replaced
        with an “F.” If this has happened to you, contact the instructor of the class right away. It is possible
        that he/she will still allow you to finish the work you are missing and will change your grade once your work is graded.
        This option is at the sole discretion of the instructor, and you must contact him/her to find out whether or not
        he/she would be willing to accept work a semester or more late.</string>
    <string name="que20_content">If your classes were there one day and gone the next,
        they were most likely dropped due to lack of payment. Call the business office
        at 601-266-4137 to find out how you can fix the situation. Once you have paid the fees,
        if it is past the deadline for you to add your classes back yourself on SOAR, you must use
        the Special Permissions button in your SOAR account.
        IMPORTANT: Keep attending all your classes. If you are taking an online class,
        email your instructor and let him/her know that you have been dropped but will
        log back in as soon as you are reinstated.</string>
    <string name="que21_content">You will need to contact the instructor for the class in which you wish to enroll.
        If they allow the enrollment they will contact the School of Computing office so that we can do
        a special enrollment override.</string>
    <string name="que22_content">Please go to: http://www.usm.edu/sites/default/files/groups/office-registrar/images/
        onlinepermissiontoaddafterthedeadlinefinal.pdf</string>
    <string name="que23_content">There are three reasons that you might not be able to register:

    1. Your window is not open. To check when your SOAR window will be open, look on your student center page for enrollment dates.
    2. You have not been advised. Only your advisor (or the School of Computing office with permission from your advisor)
        can click your Eligible To Enroll button. Please contact your advisor and make an appointment.
    3. You have a hold on your account. To check to see if you have a hold, look on your student services
        page for a Do-Not-Enter sign. Clicking this will tell you the reason for the hold. If it is financial,
        please contact business services at 266-4774. If you are on probation continued or suspension,
        you will need to talk to your advisor  and sign a contract detailing your plans for improving your grades.
</string>
    <string name="que24_content">If you need someone to talk to, Student Counseling Services is the place to go.
        You can visit their web site or call them during business hours at (601) 266-4829.
        If it\'s after 5:00pm or on a weekend and you need to talk to someone right away, please call 601-606-HELP (4357).</string>
    <string name="que25_content">Your first resource is your instructor. Instructors hold office hours each
        week specifically to help students who are having trouble. They will be happy to answer any questions
        you have about the lecture or to go over assignments and suggest areas for improvement.
        If you\'re having trouble with your writing, another resource is the Writing Center, located in Cook Library
        right next to Starbucks. The Writing Center has tutors who will talk with you about your writing project
        and help you figure out what you want to say and how you can say it most effectively.
        To make an appointment at the Writing Center, please call 601-266-4821.
</string>
    <string name="que26_content">The Writing Center in Cook Library is a great resource for helping you sort out your thoughts
        and get started on your paper, no matter what class it\'s for.  To make an appointment to talk with a tutor,
        please call 601-266-4821.</string>
    <string name="que27_content">The Learning Enhancement Center\'s Student Help Page will get you started with everything
        from how to log in to Blackboard to how to turn in assignments.</string>
    <string name="que28_content">The best way to avoid being accused of plagiarism is not to plagiarize.
        Fortunately, avoiding plagiarism is fairly simple: if you use phrases or sentences that you did not write yourself,
        put them in quotation marks and cite your source. If you copy anything and paste it into your paper,
        use quotation marks and cite your source. If you copy something but change the wording and the order,
        this is paraphrasing. You won\'t need to use quotation marks, but you still need to cite your source.
        If you read a great argument that you want to use in your own paper, cite your source.
        If you want to use a few sentences or a paragraph from a paper you wrote for another class,
        you still need to use quotation marks and cite yourself and your previous paper as the source.
If you cite your sources and use quotation marks when necessary, you will not be accused of plagiarism.
If you use another person\'s writing without citing the source, you will be caught. The Southern Miss instructors
        subscribe to a service which, when your paper is entered, will compare it with sources all over the internet,
        published books and articles, papers from paper mills, and any student papers that have ever been submitted to it before.
        If the service finds parts of your paper that were copied from a source, they will provide a link to the source,
        so your paper and the source can be compared side by side. It is never, ever worth the risk.
        If you run out of time to write a paper, it is much better to ask for an extension or even to submit
        what you have than to plagiarize. If you fail a paper, you have an “F” on one paper,
        and still have time to bring up your grade or withdraw passing from the class. If you plagiarize,
        you may fail the entire course, or if you attempt to withdraw, you will withdraw failing,
        which counts as an “F” in your GPA. Don\'t risk it.
If you have questions about whether something constitutes plagiarism or are unsure how to cite the source properly,
        just ask your instructor.  He/she will be happy to review it with you, and probably very glad that you asked.
</string>
    <string name="que29_content">If you believe you have been unfairly accused of plagiarism,
    you should talk to your instructor as soon as you can to find out why it is that he/she feels you have plagiarized.
    If you are unable to resolve the issue with your instructor, you may make an appointment with the Director of the department.
    He will talk to you, and to your instructor, about your situation and about the grade appeal process.
    To review the grade appeal process on your own, please click here to see the relevant information from
    USM\'S Student Handbook. Please note that you must make a good-faith effort to work things out with
    your instructor before talking to the Director, because if you have not, the Director will refer you back to the instructor.
    If you are unable to resolve things with the Director, you may appeal your grade before a university committee.
    </string>



</resources>
